Contato

www.linkedin.com/in/amílcarnunes-70390632 (LinkedIn)

Principais competências

IVA (Imposto sobre o valor acrescentado)

Impostos Especiais de Consumo ISP

Languages

Português (Native or Bilingual)
Inglês (Full Professional)
Espanhol (Full Professional)
Francês (Professional Working)

Certifications

Contabilista Certificado

Amílcar Nunes

Partner | Indirect Tax | EY

Lisboa, Lisboa, Portugal

Resumo

Regular indirect tax assistance to national and international companies, including specific experience in cross-border transactions and tax planning

Regular indirect tax assistance to national and international companies, including specific experience in cross-border transactions, customs and general tax planning

Regular experience in Tax Policy projects, namely connected with consumer goods taxation (excise perspective, tobacco tax, alcohol tax, among others);

Regular assistance in compliance projects and ERP implementing systems

Significant experience of the Portuguese and European Indirect Tax Law

Regular support in tax due diligence Engagements and business transaction services compliance.

Professor at the Tax Course of University Católica Business and Economics School of Lisbon – VAT and Excise Taxes;

Experiência

EY

20 anos 8 meses

Partner

outubro de 2018 - Present (6 anos 7 meses)

Senior Manager setembro de 2004 - Present (20 anos 8 meses)

Caixa Geral de Depósitos Colaborador setembro de 2003 - setembro de 2004 (1 ano 1 mês) Lisboa

Formação acadêmica

Nova School of Business and Economics Licenciatura, Economia · (1998 - 2002)

IDEF

Pós Graduação, Fiscalidade · (2003 - 2004)

Nova School of Business and Economics Licenciatura Economia, Economia · (1998 - 2002)